Erik di Biase

Game Developer

London

Email

oberonx10@gmail.com

Contact Number

07504506395

Game developer, experienced with C++ and C# frameworks as well as game engines such as Unity and Unreal. Passionate about graphics, post-processing, and working with shaders in general using various graphics APIs like OpenGL, DirectX and Vulkan. Currently focusing on mobile AR development.

Work Experience

PASS Scheme Student

London Metropolitan University - London

October 2016 to May 2018

As a PASS Student, my role focused on providing to first year students in my same course subject with help and guidance when developing their own projects. My help mostly consisted in debugging C++, JavaScript, OpenGL and DirectX projects and sharing my knowledge of coding standards, methodologies, OOP technics and version control tools which are essential for game developers.

Gameplay Programmer Intern

Objective-Z - London

June 2017 to September 2017

My role in this Unity focused internship consisted in designing new innovative game mechanics, to be implemented in-game, providing the relative pitch documentation to my team leader, which if approved would be personally implemented by me and reviewed by my team leader.

Education

1st Class - BSc in Computer Games Programming

London Metropolitan University - London

2015 to 2018

Core Modules - 1st year		Core Modules - 3rd year	
Game Design	(78)	Prototype Development	(94)
Game Portfolio	(71)	Artificial Intelligence	(75)
Computer Gaming Hardware & Architectures	(87)	Artificial Intelligence for Games	(67)
Logic & Mathematical Techniques	(77)	Work Related Learning	(83)
Core Modules - 2nd year		Project	(87)
Graphics & Imaging	(76)		
Digital Toy Design	(71)		
Game Portfolio 2	(84)		
C++ Programming	(96)		
C++ Programming for Games	(81)		

Technical Skills

Languages

Programming Languages

C++ (3 years), C# (2 years), Javascript (2 years), Dart (1 year)

Shading Languages

GLSL (2 years), HLSL (2 years)

Markup & Style Sheet Languages

HTML (2 years), CSS (2 years)

APIs

Graphic APIs

OpenGL (2 years), DirectX (1 year), Vulkan (1 year)

Sound APIs

OpenAL (1 year), FMod (1 year)

SDKs

Augmented Reality SDKs

ARCore (1 year), Vuforia (1 year)

User Interface SDKs

Flutter

Libraries

Multimedia Libraries

GLFW (2 years), SDL (3 years), SFML (1 year)

Model Loading Libraries

ASSIMP (2 years)

Physic Libraries

BULLET (1 year)

Tools

Game Engines

Unity (2 year), Unreal Engine (1 year)

Source Control

GitHub (3 years), Jenkins (1 year)

Links

Portfolio

http://www.erikdibiase.com

Developing Team

http://www.unquestionablegames.com